

Profile

Experienced and proficient in languages that help with web development and data engineering. Gained experience and exposure from university projects, beta testing software for a digital audio workstation called "Audio Design Desk", gained certificates from courses provided, and worked on projects revolving around web development and data analytics.

Employment History

Data Engineer, Capgemini, Remote

MARCH 2022 - PRESENT

- Gain training from certificates
- Learn how to clean data, analyze data, and present it through visualizations
- Learn how to use Python libraries, such as Pandas, Tensorflow, Numpy, etc.
- Placed on projects revolving around web development and data analytics
- Satisfy the client's needs for a specific project by planning and executing effectively
- Able to use some front-end knowledge of HTML, CSS, and Javascript
- Learn to use cloud services like AWS or Azure

Beta Test Intern, Audio Design Desk, Los Angeles, CA

JANUARY 2022 - MARCH 2022

- Follow build test routines to find errors or bugs, and report them accordingly
- Test metadata software that helps organize and categorize audio files
- Close, open, or update issues within GitHub for the software
- · Report any issues or bugs to QC Lead
- Copy and paste the console log output of any bug

Education

Computer Science, California Polytechnic State University, Pomona, Pomona, CA

AUGUST 2018 - DECEMBER 2020

Graduated with a Bachelor's of Computer Science with a 3.69 GPA (Magna Cum Laude)

Joined the Game Dev Club from September 2019 - December 2019

Mathematics (AS-T), Citrus College, Glendora, CA

JUNE 2015 - JUNE 2018

Projects

URL: https://musicmaker773.github.io/portfolio/

Certifications

Google Data Analytics Specialization

Issued Dec 2022

Details

Glendora

United States 6268276044

musicmaker773@gmail.com

Links

LinkedIn

GitHub

Portfolio

Skills

Microsoft Excel

PHP

Microsoft Office

MySQL

C++

HTML & CSS

SOL

Git

JavaScript

Java

Python

Google Drive

Microsoft Power BI

AWS

Streamlit

References

Zal ColahfromAudio Design Desk

zal@add.app

Dave Johannsenfrom California State Polytechnic University, Pomona

dljohannsen@cpp.edu | 9098694195

Delfino NeirafromLos Angeles County

8054551926

Maurice BellofromUber

6268907185

Devendra PatelfromFresno County

dpatel@fresnocountyca.gov | 5594178360